A stillness gives way unto the interstice of space-time,
Its afterimage occupying the mind as the Moon above wavers to the point of breaking
None are born from the shackles of sorrow,
But from the strength within that shatters the traps which bind them
It is a requiem of atonement for the feelings put to rest and buried below,
Bound by sin and crying out in solitude for a love most tender
Pleading for absolution as grace pours out in excess,
Beyond this is an endless ritual, a mass of exultation
With the belief that the boundless lamentation
Leads to a place of happiness,
Everything might find itself having changed,
Though the serene Earth never will
Guided are those souls of yours to a tranquil land, through flames that blaze with fury
They trace a melody of admonition, toward a broken future
Strong are the wills that have turned their back on the world,
Thus we pray until they are set free