Forbidden Unrivaled Darling
Mwaaah!
Woohoo!
I can never be too careful
Will he come again today?
Anyway, I'm still a closeted idol, in my corner
Mwah!
And yet, out of all...
C'mon...
I see you sitting by the second aisle,
Always with your beautiful smile
nyan, nyan
It's dazzling me...
Woohoo!
And now...
...your red lips are getting unexpectedly, critically close to me
Love stories are branching, with no one noticing, just like in a game
I don't want love from everybody, I want you to be a fan group for me
I'll leave the stage and...
...dive into you
Let's go! To the future! Love you! Love you!
And to the past too!
Yeah!
Forbidden Unrivaled Darling
Mwaaah!
Woohoo!