Darling Darling Darling
Mwah mwah mwah
Yeah yeah
Darling Darling Darling
Mwah mwah mwah
Yeah yeah
You can adjust the divergence to any value you'd like
I'm not afraid to cheat, and neither are you, God, right?
Faster than light, even
Déjà-vu, Maisja-vu, these are the bugs I'm precisely talking about
This rewriting of the world is one of your deeds;
The program is imperfect
Love too can make you feel hot! It's a revolutionary microwave,
Ding
Yay!
So take out your phone
C'mon!
You only need to type a small, six-full-width-character-long message
One, two, three, four, five, six
And now just press the send button, let's go!
And without end:
We all are observers of our hearts' world lines
An unexpected loop of normie scenarios
We'll all hold hands,
Running toward the promised tomorrow
Convergence begins its work,
This is a La La La Labolution!
Darling Darling Darling
Mwah mwah mwah
Yeah yeah